Guide to the David Plowden Photographs and Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Photographs, 1948-2011; Series I; 189; 41.9 linear_feet
  - July 1995 Acquisition
    - Exhibition Prints
      - S. S. Richelieu (formerly S. S. Naragansett), Canada Steamship Lines at Murray Bay on Saint Lawrence River [last season of operation]. Murray Bay, Quebec, Canada (864-39), 1964 August (Box 70)
      - S. S. Richelieu, Canada Steamship Lines in Saint Lawrence River, Arriving at Murray Bay [last year of operation]. Murray Bay, Quebec, Canada (864-362), 1964 August (Box 70)
      - S. S. St. Lawrence, Canada Steamship Lines, Departing Down River [last season of operation]. Murray Bay, Quebec, Canada (864-562), 1964 August (Box 70)
      - S. S. Tadoussac, Canada Steamship Lines, in Saint Lawrence River, off La Malbaie [last season of operation]. La Malbaie, Quebec, Canada (864-465), 1964 August (Box 70)
      - S. S. Tadoussac, Canada Steamship Lines, in Saint Lawrence River off Isle Aux Coudres [last season of operation]. Quebec, Canada (864-476), 1964 August (Box 70)
      - Sidewheel Steamer Alexander Hamilton, Hudson River Day Line, Leaving Bear Mountain Landing. Bear Mountain Landing, New York (665-256), 1965 June (Box 70)
      - Stateroom, Steamer Keewatin, Canadian Pacific Railway, Great Lakes Fleet (964-558), 1964 September (Box 70)
      - Steamer City of Keansburg at Bear Mountain Landing on Hudson River, Bear Mountain Bridge in Background. Bear Mountain Landing, New York (665-220), 1965 June (Box 70)
      - Steamer City of Keansburg, Arriving at Bear Mountain Landing in Hudson River. Bear Mountain Landing, New York (665-254), 1965 June (Box 70)
      - Steamer Tadoussac, Canada Steamship Lines, Heading Down River in Saint Lawrence River, off La Malbaie [last season of operation]. La Malbaie, Quebec, Canada (864-399), 1964 August (Box 70)
      - A Deck Stairwell, Steamer Richelieu, Formerly S. S. Naragansett, Canada Steamship Lines (864-344), 1964 August (Box 71)
      - Deck Hand, New York Central Railroad, with New York Central N. 24 in background, in Hudson River. Weehawken, New Jersey (NYH-ST-NYC-263-53), 1963 February (Box 71)
      - Detail of Bed, Guest Stateroom, Steamer Kinsman Enterprise (890-160), 1990 August (Box 71)
      - Fireplace in Observation Room, Steamer Kinsman Enterprise (890-240), 1990 August (Box 71)
      - Hudson River, off Weehawken, New Jersey, Showing New York Central Railroad Steam Tugs (ST-NYC-363-70), 1963 March (Box 71)
      - New York Central Railroad Steam Tug New York Central No. 18, in Hudson River, off Weehawken. Weehawken, New Jersey (ST-NYC-363), 1963 March (Box 71)
      - New York Central Railroad Steam Tug New York Central No. 18. Weehawken, New Jersey (ST-NYC-363-102), 1963 March (Box 71)
      - New York Central Railroad Steam Tug New York Central No. 31. Weehawken, New Jersey (ST-NYC-363-170), 1963 March (Box 71)
      - New York Central Railroad Steam Tugs New York Central No. 30 on the right and New York Central No. 18 on the left, in Hudson River off Weehawken. Weehawken, New Jersey (ST-NYC-363), 1963 March (Box 71)
      - New York Central Railroad Steam Tugs New York Central No. 30 on the right and New York Central No. 18 on the left, in Hudson River off Weehawken. Weehawken, New Jersey (NYC-T-363), 1963 March (Box 71)
      - New York Central Railroad Steam Tugs No. 8 and No. 18. Weehawken, New Jersey (ST-NYC-363), 1963 March (Box 71)
      - Stack Detail, New York Central Railroad Tug New York Central No. 30. Weehawken, New Jersey (ST-NYC-363), 1963 March (Box 71)
      - Steam Tug New York Central No. 8, off Weehawken. Weehawken, New Jersey (ST-NYC-363-102), 1963 March (Box 71)
      - Wheelhouse, S. S. Richelieu, Canada Steamship Lines (864-348), 1964 August (Box 71)
      - Burlington Northern Railway, Allouez Ore Docks. Superior, Wisconsin (679-625), 1979 June (Box 72)
      - Detail, Pilot House, Steamer Lone Star, Builder's Sand Gravel Co., Mississippi River. Davenport, Iowa (964-535), 1964 September (Box 72)
      - Petersen Lighterage Co. Steam Lighter Victor, in Hudson River off Lower Manhattan. New York, New York (EL-1167-1253), 1967 November (Box 72)
      - Steamwheel Steamer Lone Star, Builder's Sand Gravel Co., on Mississippi River below Davenport. Davenport, Iowa (964-518), 1964 September (Box 72)
      - TSS Princess Marguerite, Canadian Pacific Steamship Line, off Port Angeles (retired September, 1988). Port Angeles, Washington (GFB-68-5887), 1968 (Box 72)
      - Tugboat Bronx, Harlem Transfer Company. Hoboken, New Jersey (NYH-FB/DL-53), 1960 (Box 72)
      - Unloading Cement Clinker from Steamer Kinsman Independent II. Superior, Wisconsin (685-593), 1985 June (Box 72)
      - Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul Pacific Railroad Yard with Engine Terminal. Bozeman, Montana (MLW-852-1), 1952 August (Box 73)
      - Denver and Rio Grande Railroad Freight Train Climbing Grade to Cumbres Pass. Colorado (SE-RG-160), 1962 (Box 73)
      - Duluth, Mesabi Iron Range Railroad 2-8-8-4 Type Steam Engine Locomotive. Two Harbors, Minnesota (DMIR-456-1), 1956 April (Box 73)
      - Former Milwaukee Road Depot. Parkston, South Dakota (969-864), 1969 September (Box 73)
      - Great Northern Railway Extra 3377 East. Near Atwater, Minnesota (GN-1956-9-1) (Box 73)
      - Great Northern Railway Extra 3383 East. Near Delano, Minnesota (GN-1956-9) (Box 73)
      - Great Northern Railway Extra 3387 East. Wilmar, Minnesota (GN-1956-1-2) (Box 73)
      - Great Northern Railway Extra 3387 East. Willmar, Minnesota (GN-1956-5), 1956 February (Box 73)
      - Great Northern Railway, Extra 3377 East, Grain Train. Near Atwater, Minnesota (GN-1956-10) (Box 73)
      - Northern Pacific Railway 4-6-6-4 Type Steam Locomotive Number 5122 Climbing Livingston Hill. Montana (NP-852-1), 1952 August (Box 73)
      - Northern Pacific Railway Freight Train. Near Helena, Montana (NP-852-1-4), 1952 August (Box 73)
      - Northern Pacific Railway Freight Train. Near Helena, Montana (NP-852-2), 1952 August (Box 73)
      - Northern Pacific Railway Westbound Freight Train Climbing Livingston Hill. West of Livingston, Montana (NP-852-1-7), 1952 August (Box 73)
      - Union Pacific Tracks and Depot. Cheyenne Wells, Colorado (GP-922), 1971 (Box 73)
      - Baltimore Ohio Railroad. Cumberland, Maryland (MD-963-55), 1963 September (Box 74)
      - Chesapeake Ohio,Ann Arbor Railroad Depot. Clare, Michigan (975-1609), 1975 September (Box 74)
      - Clinton, Wisconsin (880-231), 1980 August (Box 74)
      - Detail of Diesel Switch Engine, Elgin, Joliet Eastern Railroad. Whiting, Indiana (C-483-354), 1983 April (Box 74)
      - Former Erie Railroad Passenger Depot. Deposit, New York (366-3), 1966 March (Box 74)
      - Former New York, New Haven Hartford Railroad Depot. Canaan, Connecticut (CT-1163-23), 1963 November (Box 74)
      - Lehigh Valley Railroad Depot. South Plainfield, New Jersey (NJ-1263-59), 1963 December (Box 74)
      - Looking West From Baltimore Ohio Railroad Passenger Station. Cumberland, Maryland (MD-963-67), 1962 September (Box 74)
      - New York Central Railroad Freight Yard. Weehawken, New Jersey (NYC-1955-1-1) (Box 74)
      - Northbound Platform, Delaware Hudson Railroad Station. Whitehall, New York (1265-516), 1965 December (Box 74)
      - Pacific Great Eastern Railway. Lillooet, British Columbia,, Canada (GFB-2315), 1968 (Box 74)
      - Snowplow, Soo Line Railroad. Gladstone, Michigan (975-1576), 1975 September (Box 74)
      - View From Delaware Hudson Railroad Bridge. West Pawlet, Vermont (V-663-274), 1963 June (Box 74)
      - Waiting for the Arrival of the Phoebe Snow, Erie-Lackawanna Railroad. Waverly, New York (464-400), 1964 April (Box 74)
      - Woman Waiting for Train. Concord, Massachusetts (MA-263-167), 1963 December (Box 74)
      - Central Railroad of New Jersey Passenger Terminal. Jersey City, New Jersey (CNJ-467-279), 1967 April (Box 75)
      - Central Railroad of New Jersey Terminal. Jersey City, New Jersey (CNJ-467-309), 1967 April (Box 75)
      - Former Baltimore Ohio Railroad Yard Office. East Salamanca, New York (1075-247), 1975 October (Box 75)
      - Former Jersey Central Railroad Depot. Wilkes-Barre, Pennsylvania (PA-164-201), 1964 January (Box 75)
      - Former New Haven Railroad Depot. Kingston, Rhode Island (475-199), 1975 April (Box 75)
      - Former New York, New Haven Hartford Railroad Station. Canaan, Connecticut (CT-1163-36), 1963 November (Box 75)
      - Interior Waiting Room, Canadian Pacific Railroad Depot. Saint Johnsbury, Vermont (STJ-571-153), 1971 May (Box 75)
      - Outer Station, Waiting Room Detail. Reading, Pennsylvania (PA-1063-83), 1963 October (Box 75)
      - Scale, Outer Station. Reading, Pennsylvania (PA-1063), 1963 October (Box 75)
      - Ticket Office Box Window, Lehigh Valley Railroad Depot. Rochester, New York (ROCH-JCT-1159-2), 1959 October (Box 75)
      - Waiting Room, Former Chicago Eastern Illinois Railroad Depot. Princeton, Indiana (1066-526), 1966 October (Box 75)
      - Waiting Room, Reading Company Outer Station. Reading, Pennsylvania (PA-1063-27), 1963 October (Box 75)
      - Waiting Room, Reading Company Outer Station. Reading, Pennsylvania (RDG-STA-1961-1) (Box 75)
      - Central Railroad of New Jersey Commuter Trains, Jersey City Terminal. Jersey City, New Jersey (CNJ-467-274), 1967 April (Box 76)
      - Central Vermont Railway Station Trainshed. Saint Albans, Vermont (V-663-193), 1963 June (Box 76)
      - Delaware Hudson Railway FA Tower. Oneonta, New York (D, 1975 (Box 76)
      - Former Erie Railroad Passenger Depot. Susquehanna, Pennsylvania (366-1), 1966 March (Box 76)
      - Former Erie Railroad Passenger Depot. Susquehanna, Pennsylvania (366-15), 1966 March (Box 76)
      - Jersey Central Line Depot. Wilkes-Barre, Pennsylvania (PA-164-203), 1964 January (Box 76)
      - Locomotive Engineer, Delaware Hudson Railroad. Oneonta, New York (D, 1975 (Box 76)
      - Locomotive Engineer, in Cab of Diesel Locomotive, Delaware and Hudson Railroad (D, 1974 (Box 76)
      - Parked Cars in Front of Erie-Lackawanna Railroad Depot. Tenafly, New Jersey (NJ-1263-31), 1963 December (Box 76)
      - Rail Laying Crew, Penn-Central Railroad. Near Cresson, Pennsylvania (875-327), 1975 August (Box 76)
      - Sal Bagnoli, Yard Conductor, Delaware Hudson Railway. Mechanicville, New York (D, 1975 March (Box 76)
      - Switchman Coupling Cars, Delaware Hudson Railroad. Whitehall, New York (D, 1975 (Box 76)
      - Sydney Louisburg Railway, Mixed Train. Louisburg, Nova Scotia, Canada (S, 1959 August (Box 76)
      - Train and Engine Crew, Chesapeake and Ohio Railroad. Clifton Forge, Virginia (C, 1953 March (Box 76)
      - Abandoned 2-8-0 Type Locomotive, Quincy Hill Mining Company. Quincy Hill, Michigan (975-798), 1975 September (Box 77)
      - Boston Maine Railroad Train Number 3308. Claremont Junction, New Hampshire (B, 1952 February (Box 77)
      - Canadian National Railways, Hostler and Steam Locomotive on Turntable. Hamilton, Ontario (CNR-559-1), 1959 May (Box 77)
      - Canadian Pacific Railway 4-6-4 Locomotive 2822 and 2825 at The Glen Engine Terminal. Montreal, Quebec, Canada (CPR-360), 1960 March (Box 77)
      - Canadian Pacific Railway Locomotive Engineer and Fireman, The Glen Engine Terminal. Montreal, Quebec, Canada (CPR-360-102-A), 1960 March (Box 77)
      - Canadian Pacific Railway, Man Making Repairs to Locomotive Smokebox, St. Luc Engine Terminal. Montreal, Quebec, Canada (CPR-360), 1960 March (Box 77)
      - Canadian Pacific Railway. McAdam, New Brunswick, Canada (CPR-759), 1959 July (Box 77)
      - Canadian Pacific Railway. Harvey, New Brunswick, Canada (CPR-759-19), 1959 July (Box 77)
      - Hostler Cleaning Fires of Steam Locomotive, Central Vermont Railway. White River Junction, Vermont (V-865-55), 1965 August (Box 77)
      - "Hooping Up", Train Orders to Conductor, Baltimore Ohio Railroad. Harper's Ferry, West Virginia (HF-1961) (Box 77)
      - Locomotive Taking Water, Union Transportation Company. New Egypt, New Jersey (UTC), 1961 (Box 77)
      - Southern Railway Freight Train Passing Depot. Orange, Virginia (OR-1961) (Box 77)
      - Sydney Louisburg Railway. Glace Bay, Nova Scotia, Canada (S, 1959 August (Box 77)
      - Yard Conductor "Pulling Pin", Delaware Hudson Railroad Freight Yard. Mechanicville, New York (D, 1975 (Box 77)
      - Canadian Pacific Railway 4-6-2 Type Steam Locomotive Number 2408 on Local Passenger Train. Vaudreuil, Quebec, Canada (CPR-360-2408), 1960 March (Box 78)
      - Canadian Pacific Railway 4-6-4 Type Steam Locomotive Number 2811. Montreal, Quebec, Canada (CPR-360-2811), 1960 March (Box 78)
      - Canadian Pacific Railway Conductor Handing Orders to Engineer. Montreal, Quebec, Canada (CPR-360-B), 1960 March (Box 78)
      - Canadian Pacific Railway Locomotive Number 1201 in Snow Storm, The Glen Engine Terminal. Montreal, Quebec, Canada (CPR-360-30), 1960 March (Box 78)
      - Canadian Pacific Railway Passenger Trains, Windsor Station. Windsor Station, Montreal, Quebec, Canada (CPR-360-5), 1960 March (Box 78)
      - Canadian Pacific Railway, The Glen Engine Terminal. Montreal, Quebec, Canada (CPR-360-102), 1960 March (Box 78)
      - Central Vermont Railway 2-10-4 Type Locomotive Number 707 on Turntable. White River Junction, Vermont (CV-1957-5) (Box 78)
      - Central Vermont Railway Engine Number 501. Brattleboro, Vermont (CV-1957-2) (Box 78)
      - Reading Company Locomotives 2100 and 12102. Point Clinton, Pennsylvania (IHR-1063-73), 1963 October (Box 78)
      - Sydney Louisburg Railway Yards and Steel Mills. Glace Bay, Nova Scotia, Canada (S, 1959 August (Box 78)
      - Canadian National Railway 0-8-0 Type Steam Locomotive Leaving Roundhouse at Hamilton, Ontario, Canada on Last Day of Operation. Hamilton, Ontario, Canda (CPR-559), 1959 May (Box 79)
      - Canadian Pacific Railway 2-8-2 Type Locomotive # 5145. Montreal, Quebec, Canada (CPR-360), 1960 March (Box 79)
      - Canadian Pacific Railway G-3g Class 4-6-2 Type, Steam Locomotive, Detail of Driving Wheels. Montreal, Quebec, Canada (CPR-360-9), 1960 March (Box 79)
      - Canadian Pacific Railway Locomotive Number 5145 in Roundhouse. Montreal, Quebec, Canada (CPR-360-5145), 1960 March (Box 79)
      - Canadian Pacific Railway Locomotive Taking Coal. Brownville Junction, Maine (CPR-759-1), 1959 July (Box 79)
      - Canadian Pacific Railway Locomotives in Roundhouse, The Glen Engine Terminal. Montreal, Quebec, Canada (CPR-360), 1960 March (Box 79)
      - Canadian Pacific Railway, The Glen Engine Terminal. Montreal, Quebec, Canada (CPR-360), 1960 March (Box 79)
      - Driving Wheels, CNR 4-8-4 Type Steam Locomotive Number #6218 at Central Vermont Railway Terminal. White River Junction, Vermont (V-865-14), 1965 August (Box 79)
      - Former Lake Superior Ishpeming Railway 2-8-0 Type Steam Engine, Detail of Driving Wheel and Valve Gear. Marquette, Michigan (679-592), 1979 June (Box 79)
      - Quebec Central Railway (Canadian Pacific) Freight Train. Near Vallee Junction, Quebec, Canada (CPR-360-D), 1960 March (Box 79)
      - Reading Company Driving Wheels 4-8-4 Type Steam Locomotive (372-15), 1972 March (Box 79)
      - Chicago Eastern Illinois Railroad Depot. Princeton, Indiana (1066-63), 1966 October (Box 80)
      - Chicago Eastern Illinois Railroad Depot waiting room. Princeton, Indiana (1066-59), 1966 October (Box 80)
      - Corn Crib in Soy Bean Field Near Grand Junction, Greene County, Iowa (686-1102), 1986 June (Box 80)
      - Faxon, Oklahoma (GFB-68-2870), 1968 (Box 80)
      - Former Colorado Southern Railroad Tracks. Grenville, New Mexico (471-452), 1971 April (Box 80)
      - Gathering Maple Sap (Sugaring), Cutting Farm. Guilford, Vermont (V-366), 1966 March (Box 80)
      - Harvested Wheat Fields. Near Dusty, Washington (CP-1194), 1973 (Box 80)
      - LaCrosse, Wisconsin (CP-93), 1973 (Box 80)
      - Pipe Line Bridge, Colorado River. Between Topock, Arizona and California (GFB-68-3988-A), 1968 (Box 80)
      - Railroad Tracks. South of Chicago, Illinois (282-309), 1982 February (Box 80)
      - Steamer Kinsman Independent II. Duluth, Minnesota (685-544), 1985 June (Box 80)
      - Steamer S. T. Crapo, Inland Lakes Management, in Lake Michigan off Waukegan, Illinois (1185-21), 1985 November (Box 80)
      - Steamer Tadoussac in Saint Lawrence River off L'Isle-aux-Coudres, Quebec. Quebec, Canada (864-476), 1964 August (Box 80)
      - Storefronts. Keokuk, Iowa (CP-1224), 1973 (Box 80)
      - Trackside Buildings. Ironwood, Michigan (680-574), 1980 June (Box 80)
      - Abandoned Barn. Near Drake, North Dakota (CP-738), 1973 (Box 81)
      - Barn. Isabella County, Michigan (975-148), 1975 September (Box 81)
      - Barn. Marion, Wayne County, New York (WC-218), 1966 (Box 81)
      - Cow Barn Interior. Isabella County, Michigan (975-691), 1975 September (Box 81)
      - Cow by Stone Wall. Walden, Vermont (STJ-571-307), 1971 May (Box 81)
      - Farm. Cap Lumière, New Brunswick, Canada (GFB-69-1534), 1969 (Box 81)
      - Hoven Headstone. South Dakota (GP-1856), 1971 (Box 81)
      - Interior, Round Barn, Roof Detail. Isabella County, Michigan (975-712), 1975 September (Box 81)
      - Section Road. Scott County, Iowa (486-120), 1986 April (Box 81)
      - The Rockville Bridge, Susquehanna River. North of Enola, Pennsylvania (GFB-469-235), 1969 April (Box 81)
      - Warehouse. Mountain Home, Idaho (874-1437), 1974 August (Box 81)
      - Wells Street Looking North. Chicago, Illinois (181-60), 1981 January (Box 81)
      - Beneath Dan Ryan Expressway. Chicago, Illinois (HDP-2138), 1966 (Box 82)
      - Chicago, Illinois (1079-221), 1979 October (Box 82)
      - Chicago, Illinois (281-176), 1981 February (Box 82)
      - Chicago, Illinois (980-28), 1980 September (Box 82)
      - Elk Grove Village, Illinois (C-383-25), 1983 March (Box 82)
      - Former New Haven Railroad Bridge, Cape Cod Canal. Buzzards Bay, Massachusetts (865-159), 1965 August (Box 82)
      - Geronimo, Oklahoma (GFB-69-1541), 1969 (Box 82)
      - Iron Pratt Truss, Buffalo Creek. Bethany County, West Virginia (GFB-68-1322), 1968 (Box 82)
      - New York City Lower Manhattan Skyline from Jersey City, New Jersey (NJ-164-73), 1964 (Box 82)
      - Portage Viaduct, Genesee River. Portageville, New York (GFB-68-3120), 1968 (Box 82)
      - West Street. New York, New York (HDP-941), 1966 (Box 82)
      - Woonsocket, Rhode Island (1174-132), 1974 November (Box 82)
      - Chicago, Illinois (1079-947), 1979 October (Box 83)
      - Chicago, Illinois (C-483-145), 1983 April (Box 83)
      - Erie Canal, improved version, detail, Schoharie Creek aqueduct. Fort Hunter, New York (NYS-1067), 1967 October (Box 83)
      - Factory Buildings North of the Loop. Chicago, Illinois (C-483-61), 1983 (Box 83)
      - Former South Royalton House. South Royalton, Vermont (V-364-195), 1964 March (Box 83)
      - Grain Elevator, Lake Calumet. Chicago, Illinois (C-1082-508), 1982 October (Box 83)
      - LaCrosse, Wisconsin (CP-253-A), 1973 (Box 83)
      - Laura Beck (Mrs. John Beck). Culbertson, Montana (GP-456), 1971 (Box 83)
      - Northeast Freeway. Atlanta, Georgia (HDP-3279), 1966 (Box 83)
      - Sodus Point. Wayne County, New York (WC-218), 1966 (Box 83)
      - Unfinished Freeway. Atlanta, Georgia (HDP-3603), 1966 (Box 83)
      - Valmy, Nevada (CP-1693), 1973 (Box 83)
      - Canadian National Railways Engineer Oiling Locomotive. Hamilton, Ontario, Canada (CNR-559), 1959 May (Box 84)
      - Canadian Pacific Railway 4-6-2 type locomotive #1262. Montreal, Quebec, Canada (CPR-360-1262), 1960 March (Box 84)
      - Canadian Pacific Railway, Driving Wheels, Locomotive #5145. Montreal, Quebec, Canada (CPR-360), 1960 March (Box 84)
      - Doorway. Chipman's Point, Vermont (FBA-V-W-(663)-53), 1963 (Box 84)
      - Ferry Roaring Bull, Susquehanna River Ferry. Millersburg, Pennsylvania (FBA-S-562-25), 1962 (Box 84)
      - Ferryboat Orange, Newburgh-Beacon Ferry, Hudson River. Approaching Newburgh, New York. (NBF-1163-182), 1962 November (Box 84)
      - Herkimer, New York (1073-357), 1973 October (Box 84)
      - Home with porch. South Royalton, Vermont (V-NH 865), 1962 (Box 84)
      - House. Deep River, Iowa (386-221), 1986 March (Box 84)
      - Steamer Lone Star, last authentic Mississippi River steam tour boat. On Mississippi River off Davenport, Iowa (964-391), 1964 September (Box 84)
      - Stern wheel, Steamer Delta Queen. Rock Island, Illinois (964-646), 1964 September (Box 84)
      - Commercial Block. Richmond, Virginia (467-802), 1967 April (Box 85)
      - Company Houses. Cohoes, New York (1076-284), 1976 October (Box 85)
      - Davy, West Virginia (374-1144), 1974 March (Box 85)
      - Face on back of Turbine, State Line Power Plant. Chicago, Illinois (C-1083-31), 1983 October (Box 85)
      - Former Chesapeake Ohio Railroad Depot. Delaware, Ohio (564-42), 1964 May (Box 85)
      - Former Soo Line Railroad (abandoned) ore dock. Marquette, Michigan (975-850), 1975 September (Box 85)
      - Milwaukee, Wisconsin (1085-808), 1985 October (Box 85)
      - Rolling Mill Steel Mill, Indiana Harbor. East Chicago, Indiana (IS-2215), 1979 (Box 85)
      - [Site where the of body of Bobby Franks, victim in Leopold and Loeb case, was found]. Whiting, Indiana (C-482-131), 1982 April (Box 85)
      - Steel Works, Indiana Harbor Canal, Steamer Marlhill Unloading Taconite Pellets. East Chicago, Indiana (IS-2), 1979 (Box 85)
      - Taconite Plant, National Steel. Keewatin, Minnesota (679-372), 1979 June (Box 85)
      - U.S. Steel Gary Works. Gary, Indiana (C-483-457), 1983 April (Box 85)
      - Coils of Steel, UNR-Leavitt Corp. Chicago, Illinois (C-682-275), 1982 June (Box 86)
      - Grain Elevators and Feed Mill. Apache, Oklahoma (969-394), 1969 September (Box 86)
      - Grain Elevators and Silos. Russell, Kansas (969-98), 1969 September (Box 86)
      - Loading surplus wheat into hold of Liberty Ship bound for Hudson River Reserve Fleet (Jones Point, New York). Weehawken, New Jersey (RFG 1-A-6), 1961 (Box 86)
      - Rolling Mill Steel Mill, Indiana Harbor. East Chicago, Indiana (IS-1825), 1979 (Box 86)
      - Steel Mill, Basic Oxygen Furnace (IS-2171), 1979 (Box 86)
    - Reproducible Prints and Study Prints
      The original boxes that housed these prints included inscriptions that generally identified their contents. These inscriptions include:
      Box 87: Rural subjects, such as barns, farms, and grain elevators
      Box 89: Towns
      Box 90: Bridges
      Box 92: Maritime subjects, including the Great Lakes, and railroads
      Box 93: Reprinted duplicate prints
      Box 94: Industrial subjects, including steel manufacturing, and Chicago, Illinois
      Box 96: Bridges
      Box 97: Image numbers with prefix HDP, probably related to The Freeway in the City (Washignton, D.C.: United States Government Printing Office, 1968)
      Box 98: Miscellaneous prints for Yale, including churches and images of the Midwest
      Box 100: Railroad stations
      Box 101: Vermont barns
      Box 102: Ferries Box
      Box 103: Boats
      Box 104: Bridges
      Box 105: Related to Abraham Lincoln
      Box 106: Steel industry
      Box 107: Industrial landscapes
      Box 109: Chicago, Illinois, portraits, neighborhoods, and environmental changes
      Box 115: Bridges
      Box 116: Bridges
      - Abandoned Barn. Isabella County, Michigan (975-641) Reproducible print, 1975 September (Box 87)
      - Abandoned Barn and Silo. Clare County, Michigan (975-1784) Reproducible print, 1975 September (Box 87)
      - Abandoned Barn. Isabella County, Michigan (975-2394) Reproducible (plus) print, 1975 September (Box 87)
      - Abandoned Farm. Near Symerton, Will County, Illinois (1180-48) Reproducible print, 1980 November (Box 87)